Department of Economics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Economics fonds
1964 - 1984
F-8
3.88 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Economics
The Department of Economics and Commerce was established by the Board of Governors in February 1964, and began to offer courses within the Faculty of Arts leading to B.A., M.A., and Ph.D. degrees when the University opened in 1965. The Department was responsible, through its Head, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in the fields of economics and commerce.
The Department expanded rapidly in size, growing from an initial 5 faculty members in 1965 to 52 in 1979. During this period it had greatly expanded its program offerings, including the important addition of a Master of Business Administration program in 1968. In September 1979 the Department underwent a re-organization, when it was subsumed by the new School of Business Administration and Economics in the Faculty of Arts. The School consisted of two departments: Business Administration and Economics. The School existed only until November 1981, when a separate Faculty of Business Administration was established. The Department of Economics has continued to exist in the Faculty of Arts.
The Department was administered by a Chair and departmental committees, whose number and composition changed over time. The Chair was responsible for the overall administration of the Department, and reported to the Dean of Arts. In addition to its departmental committees, the Department adopted in 1969 a Constitution and By-laws for its Graduate Program in Economics. It stated that the Program would have three committees: the Graduate Studies Committee, the Curriculum Committee, and the Admissions Committee.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body
The fonds of the Department of Economics consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curricula and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda and minutes, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, case files, memoranda, and reports.
The titles and arrangement of series and subseries were provided by the archivist.
Hoyt, George C.; Okuda, Kenji; Schoner, Bertram; Copes, Parzival; Munro, John M.; Herzog, John P.
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department of Economics in the early 1980s.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed (as of September 2002: 5.67 m., 1975-1995). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
For more information on the Department of Economics consult the following fonds:
- Faculty of Business Administration fonds, F-42
- Institute of Fisheries Analysis fonds, F-240
- inventory of the Faculty of Arts fonds, F-2
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Policies and procedures, 1965 - 1977; F-8-1; 3 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records generated in the development of Department policies and procedures. It includes memoranda, policies and procedures.
  Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  A file list is available.
  - Departmental planning, 1965 - 1969; F-8-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Constitution and by-laws, 1969 - 1977; F-8-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
  - Policies and procedures, 1973 - 1975; F-8-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
- Correspondence, 1965 - 1980; F-8-2; 1.01 m of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence received and sent by the Department Chair. It includes memoranda and reports.
  - Chronological correspondence, 1969 - 1978; F-8-2-1; 75 cm of textual records
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-8-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-8-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-8-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-8-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-8-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-8-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-8-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-8-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-8-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-8-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-8-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 8-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-8-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 8-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-8-2-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence (confidential), 1973; F-8-2-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 8-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-8-2-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence (confidential), 1974; F-8-2-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-8-2-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-8-2-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-8-2-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-8-2-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1975; F-8-2-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 8-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-8-2-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-8-2-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-8-2-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-8-2-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-8-2-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 8-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-8-2-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-8-2-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-8-2-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
  - Memoranda, 1965 - 1979; F-8-2-2; 9 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences; Office of the Vice-President, Academic and Provost
    - Dean of Arts, 1977 - 1979; F-8-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Dean of Arts Search Committee, 1976; F-8-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Vice-President, Academic, 1976 - 1979; F-8-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chairship, 1966 - 1979; F-8-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chair's correspondence, 1965 - 1974; F-8-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chair's correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-8-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
    - Chair's correspondence, 1977 - 1979; F-8-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 8-7)
  - Subject files, 1967 - 1980; F-8-2-3; 13 cm of textual records
    Center for Research in Security Prices; Human Resources
    - Acute report - Rudrum/Page, 1979 - 1980; F-8-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Centre for Research in security prices, 1977 - 1978; F-8-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Continuing education programs, 1974 - 1979; F-8-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Grade appeals - Commerce 478, 1971; F-8-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Graduate program - comprehensive exams, 1977; F-8-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - International students, 1974 - 1977; F-8-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Personnel, 1973 - 1980; F-8-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Program development, 1976 - 1978; F-8-2-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Proposed courses - law related, 1976 - 1980; F-8-2-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Training program for officials of underdeveloped countries, 1967 - 1969; F-8-2-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Undergraduate program, 1979; F-8-2-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 8-8)
    - Youth employment program, 1976 - 1978; F-8-2-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Printed materials and reports, 1965 - 1971; F-8-2-4; 3 cm of textual records
    - Discussion papers, 1967 - 1971; F-8-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
    - Printed material, 1970 - 1971; F-8-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
    - Report on scholarly activities, 1965 - 1967; F-8-2-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
- Faculty members, 1964 - 1984; F-8-3; 1.48 m of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the appointment, salary, and tenure of faculty members, as well as research grants. It includes correspondence, curricula vitae, memoranda and reports.
  - Faculty members, 1980; F-8-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - A, 1969 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - B, 1975; F-8-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - B, 1973 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - B, 1965 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - B, 1967 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - B, 1970 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 8-9)
  - Faculty - B, 1975 - 1979; F-8-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1975 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1974 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1969 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1967 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1968 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1973 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1972 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - B, 1974 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - C, 1974 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - C, 1969 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - C, 1976 - 1980; F-8-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 8-10)
  - Faculty - C, 1973 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1976 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1978 - 1980; F-8-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1970 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1970 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1966 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1967 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1967 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - C, 1970; F-8-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 8-11)
  - Faculty - D, 1976 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - D, 1976; F-8-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - D, 1966 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - D, 1966 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - D, 1971 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - D, 1968 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - E, 1969 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - E, 1970 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - F, 1966 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - F, 1973 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - G, 1976 - 1978; F-8-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - G, 1975 - 1978; F-8-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - G, 1976 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - G, 1965 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 8-12)
  - Faculty - G, 1974 - 1978; F-8-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - G, 1975; F-8-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - G, 1966 - 1967; F-8-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - G, 1965 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1965 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1975 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1970 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1967 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1972; F-8-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1967 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1967 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1965 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 8-13)
  - Faculty - H, 1970 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - H, 1972 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - I, 1966 - 1968; F-8-3-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - J, 1975 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - J, 1973; F-8-3-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - J, 1975; F-8-3-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - J, 1970 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - K, 1970 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - K, 1965 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - K, 1972 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - K, 1970 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - L, 1976 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - L, 1970 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - L, 1973 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 8-14)
  - Faculty - L, 1975; F-8-3-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - L, 1976 - 1978; F-8-3-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - L, 1974; F-8-3-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1973; F-8-3-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1973 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1974; F-8-3-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1965 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1972 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1970 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1972 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1974; F-8-3-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1975; F-8-3-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1976 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 8-15)
  - Faculty - M, 1964 - 1968; F-8-3-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 8-1)
  - Faculty - M, 1969 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 8-16)
  - Faculty - M, 1968 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 8-16)
  - Faculty - M, 1968 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 8-16)
  - Faculty - M, 1976 - 1984; F-8-3-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 8-16)
  - Faculty - M, 1970 - 1978; F-8-3-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 8-16)
  - Faculty - N, 1966 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 8-16)
  - Faculty - N, 1972 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - O, 1966 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1976 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1972 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1973 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1967 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1979 - 1980; F-8-3-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1967 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1967 - 1970; F-8-3-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - P, 1974; F-8-3-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - R, 1966 - 1967; F-8-3-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - R, 1966 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - R, 1975 - 1976; F-8-3-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - R, 1970 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - S, 1976; F-8-3-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - S, 1964 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 8-17)
  - Faculty - S, 1970 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1967 - 1975; F-8-3-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1970 - 1972; F-8-3-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1971 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1974; F-8-3-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1975 - 1977; F-8-3-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1967 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 8-18)
  - Faculty - S, 1968 - 1969; F-8-3-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - S, 1973; F-8-3-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - S, 1971 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - S, 1973 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1979; F-8-3-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - S, 1965 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - T, 1969 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - U, 1967 - 1971; F-8-3-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - V, 1979 - 1980; F-8-3-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Faculty - V, 1971 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 8-19)
  - Appointment recommendations, 1966 - 1967; F-8-3-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Appointment recommendations, 1967; F-8-3-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Appointment recommendations, 1967; F-8-3-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Appointment recommendations, 1968; F-8-3-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Salary review, 1971 - 1973; F-8-3-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Salary review - external, 1973 - 1974; F-8-3-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Academic policy 31 - disclosure forms, 1972 - 1979; F-8-3-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
  - Appointment correspondence, 1976 - 1979; F-8-3-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 8-20)
- Departmental committees, 1966 - 1979; F-8-4; 32 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records of various departmental committees. It incudes circulars, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and memoranda.
  - Appointment committee, 1969 - 1976; F-8-4-1; 5 cm of textual records
    - Appointment committee, 1969 - 1971; F-8-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Appointment committee, 1972; F-8-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Appointment committee, 1973; F-8-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Appointment committee, 1974; F-8-4-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Appointment committee, 1975 - 1976; F-8-4-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
  - Constitution committee, 1969; F-8-4-2; 1 cm of textual records
    - Constitution committee, 1969; F-8-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
  - Departmental committee, 1967 - 1976; F-8-4-3; 4 cm of textual records
    - Departmental meetings, 1967 - 1970; F-8-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Departmental meetings, 1971 - 1972; F-8-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Departmental meetings, 1973; F-8-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
    - Departmental meetings, 1974 - 1976; F-8-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
  - Economic Theory committee, 1966 - 1967; F-8-4-4; 1 cm of textual records
    - Economic theory committee, 1966 - 1967; F-8-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
  - Executive committee, 1969 - 1978; F-8-4-5; 4 cm of textual records
    - Executive committee, 1969 - 1970; F-8-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Executive committee, 1971; F-8-4-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Executive committee, 1972; F-8-4-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-22)